Fight to be seen
Above the Shadows is a fantasy, romance film directed by Claudia Myers.
A young woman who has faded to the point of becoming invisible must find
her way back with the help of the one man who can see her.
Holly, played by Olivia Thirlby.
Shayne Blackwell, played by Alan Ritchson.
Paul Jederman, played by Jim Gaffigan.
Victoria Jederman, played by Maria Dizzia.
Juliana, played by Megan Fox.
Attila, played by Tito Ortiz.
Above the Shadows is a 2019 supernatural romance film
written and directed by Claudia Myers.
The film stars Olivia Thirlby, Alan Ritchson, Jim Gaffigan, Maria Dizzia, Tito
Ortiz, David Johansen in his final feature film and Megan Fox.
It had its world premiere at the Brooklyn Film Festival on May 31, 2019, and was released to
video on demand and select theaters on July 19, 2019, by Gravitas Ventures.
The film explores themes of invisible, invisible person, invisibility.
The tone is emotional.